army-of-brides.com 2018-07-02

# Privacy Policy Information for www.army-of-brides.com

  * ### What information we collect and how it is used

We use standard web server log files and **cookie* technology**. When you visit the our web site, we capture the internet provider's domain name, country that you came from, your browser type.

We collect personal information that you choose to provide voluntarily when using or registering with us. Personal information includes information that can identify you as a specific individual, such as your name or email address.

We use this information to help us count visitors and evaluate our site's technical capacity; to arrange the web-site in the most user-friendly way, keep the site browser-friendly, to make our pages more useful to our visitors; to communicate special offers and featured items to you, to respond to your question or suggestions.

The security of your personal information is very important to us and we are committed to protecting the information we collect. Army-Of-Brides.com uses firewalls and has security measures in place at its physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our web site. We never sell or rent your personal information to any third parties under any circumstances.

***A cookie** is a small piece of information sent by a website that is saved on your hard disk by your computer's browser. It holds information a site may need to personalize your experience and to gather web site statistical data, such as which pages are visited, what is downloaded, the internet provider's domain name and country that our visitors come from. Cookies do not capture your individual email address or any private information about you. We record information on site traffic but not information on individual visitors to our site, so no information about you in particular will be kept or used. 

### Mailing Lists

When you send us an email, we use your email address to reply to your question, and we will store your communication and our reply in case we correspond further. Beyond our initial reply, we will never use your email address to send you any unsolicited message or information, nor will we share it with or sell it to anyone else for such use.

When you request information or other services, we use your email address and any other information you give us to provide you with the information or other services you requested until you ask us to stop (using the 'unsubscribe' instructions provided on the site where you signed up and/or as we otherwise provide), or until the information or service is no longer available. We will not use your address or other information to provide you with any unsolicited message or information (unless that is part of the service you are requesting), nor will we share it with or sell, rent or lease it to any third party for such use. 

### How you can decide what communication you will receive from us

Army-Of-Brides.com may send you email messages describing updates, new features, promotional offers related to this web site, notifications about new mail from its female clients, texts of your letters and women's replies **if you choose to receive such messages**. You can choose to stop receiving emails from Army-Of-Brides at any time through special Account Options link inside your account. If you do not choose to receive informational emails, the only email messages you will receive from us will be to respond to email inquiries that you send us. 

### How to update or correct your personal information

To modify your personal information, use special link Update Profile inside your account. To delete your personal information, contact us through special link Support Center inside your account.
